{
    "subject": "resource/Steve_Lavin",
    "predicate": "property/dateOfBirth",
    "object": "1964-09-04",
    "human_readable": "Steve Lavin was born on September 4, 1964.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8875223994255066,
            "question": "Did Steve Lavin have a birthday in September?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8839645385742188,
            "question": "When was Steve Lavin born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7662672400474548,
            "question": "Was Steve Lavin born before or after 1960?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7525922060012817,
            "question": "What is Steve Lavin's birth year?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7504367232322693,
            "question": "What is Steve Lavin's birth date?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7495609521865845,
            "question": "What month was Steve Lavin born in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6945570111274719,
            "question": "What day of the month was Steve Lavin born on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4991897940635681,
            "question": "Is Steve Lavin's birthday in the first half of the year?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.459796279668808,
            "question": "In what year did Steve Lavin come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43932145833969116,
            "question": "Is Steve Lavin's birthday in the summer or winter?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Steve Lavin was born on September 4, 1964.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2340_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what year did Steve Lavin come into the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2340_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Steve Lavin's birthday in the first half of the year?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2340_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What day of the month was Steve Lavin born on?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2340_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2340_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2340_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2340_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2340_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2340_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2340_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2340_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2340_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2340_95.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2340_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents contain multiple sources confirming that Steve Lavin was indeed born on September 4, 1964."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\nThe documents provide multiple references that confirm Steve Lavin was indeed born on September 4, 1964."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}